barrett-jackson.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy

Barrett-Jackson Privacy Policy 

**Last Updated: December 23, 2019** This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Barrett-Jackson Auction Company, LLC (“Barrett-Jackson” or “we”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites, mobile apps and other online services, including any Wi-Fi service we make available at our events (collectively, “Services”) or when you otherwise interact with us, including when you register for or attend one of our events, transact business at our Showroom, or when you contact us for customer support. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email). For information about choices we provide in connection with our information practices, please see the “Your Choices” section below. 

If you are a California resident, please see “Information for California Consumers” below. 

Collection of Information 

**Information You Provide to Us**  
We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you register to become a bidder, request to or consign a vehicle, create an online account, register to access our Wi-Fi service, make a purchase, participate in a contest or promotion, submit a registration or application form, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, phone number, physical address, payment method information, driver’s license information and any other information you choose to provide. 

**Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services**  
When you use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including: 

  * **Usage Information:** We collect information about your use of our online Services, including which features you interact with, purchases you make, and similar usage information. 
  * **Wi-Fi Service Information:** When you access our Wi-Fi service at one of our events, we may collect information about your use of that service, including URLs you access, search terms, information about files you access, and information about the senders and recipients of unencrypted communications you send and receive. We will only use this information to investigate or discover actual or potential violations of our user agreements or to protect the rights, property and safety of Barrett-Jackson or others. 
  * **Device Information:** We collect information about the mobile device you use to access our mobile apps, including hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information. 
  * **Log Information:** We collect server logs in connection with your use of our Services, which include IP address, the specific action taken through our Services, the date and time of the action, and web browser type and language. 
  * **Event Location Information:** When you attend one of our events, we may use the MAC address of your device and your proximity to our Wi-Fi access points, to determine your device’s location. Please see "Your Choices" below for more information. 
  * **RFID Tag Information:** The credentials we provide our VIPs, bidders, consignors, and other select customers or attendees may contain an RFID tag. These tags are small radio chips that can be read by scanners at our events. Each tag contains a unique code that is associated with each person using the credential, allowing us to facilitate entry into restricted areas and provide certain benefits or services to those individuals. 
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We may use various technologies to collect information in connection with your use of our websites and mobile apps, including the following: 
    * _Cookies_ , which are small files that are sent to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website, and are used to recognize your browser and track your usage each time you visit; 
    * _Mobile device identifiers_ , which are unique identifiers established by your mobile device operating system that we collect from our mobile apps. These identifiers are used for similar purposes as cookies; 
    * _Local storage_ , which stores data locally in your browser or device, including user preferences; and 
    * _Pixel tags_ , which are small blocks of code often used in connection with cookies. Pixel tags (or web beacons) may be placed on our websites and emails and allow us to track website usage and determine when emails have been opened and acted upon. 

**Information We Collect From Other Sources**  
We may also obtain information from other sources. For instance, we may receive information about you from corporate sponsors or partners that attend the events and from third parties that sell tickets to our events. Additionally, if you link your Barrett-Jackson account with an account you have with a social media service (such as Facebook), we will have access to certain information from that service, such as your name, profile image, and other account information, in accordance with the authorization procedures established by that service. 

We may combine the information we collect about you and use this information for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide and improve our events, products and services; 
  * Send you technical notices and support and administrative messages; 
  * Communicate with you about products, services, promotions, events and other news and information we think will be of interest to you; 
  * Personalize our Services and events, including by providing content, advertisements or features we think will be of interest to you; 
  * Facilitate contests and promotions and process and deliver prizes; 
  * Monitor and analyze trends and usage in connection with our Services and events; 
  * Detect and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Barrett-Jackson and others; and 
  * Carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information was collected. 

We may share information about you as follows: 

  * If you are a resident of a state other than California, we may share your information with our select partners or sponsors that may use this information to send you marketing they think will be of interest to you, including any sponsor identified on the page you use to register to access our Wi-Fi service; 
  * With service providers who access the information in connection with the services they perform for us; 
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process; 
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Barrett-Jackson or others; 
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; 
  * If you are a consignor/seller or winning bidder/buyer of a vehicle at one of our events, your contact information will be shared with the other party to the transaction; and 
  * With your consent or at your direction. 

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information with third parties, which cannot reasonably be used by those third parties to identify you. 

Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others 

We allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and in mobile apps. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of our websites and mobile apps and other websites and apps, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Barrett-Jackson and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our websites and mobile apps and other websites and apps, and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to learn how you may be able to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. Your mobile device may also include a feature that allows you to opt out of having certain information collected through apps used for behavioral advertising purposes. Please review the settings of your mobile device for more information. 

**Account Information**  
You may update the online account information you provide to us by logging into your online account. 

**Cookies**  
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our websites. 

**Promotional Communications**  
You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations. 

**Event Location Information**  
Please contact us at: [egal@barrett-jackson.com](mailto:legal@barrett-jackson.com) if you want to opt out of our collection of location information when you attend an event. We will need you to provide us with your device MAC address to facilitate this opt out. This opt out will only work for each unique MAC address, so you will need to opt out for each device you bring to an event. And any device that periodically resets its MAC address will be treated as a new device that requires a new opt-out. Keep in mind, you can also turn off all WiFi and Bluetooth signals to avoid collection of this information. 

**RFID Tags**  
If you are attending one of our events and are provided a credential for access to restricted areas at the event, you may request to receive a credential that does not contain an RFID tag. Please submit your request to us prior to attending the event through the information listed in the “Contact Us” section below. 

Information for California Consumers 

This section provides details about rights afforded to California consumers under the California Consumer Privacy Act or “CCPA,” and supplemental information about the personal information we collect about California consumers. 

In the last 12 months, we collected the following categories of personal information: identifiers (such as name, contact information and device identifiers); commercial information (such as products purchased); internet or other network activity information (such as browsing behavior); geolocation data; electronic, visual or similar information (such as profile image); and inferences made by us (such as shopping or event preferences). For more details about the personal information we collect, including the categories of sources, please see the Collection of Information section above. We collect this information for the business and commercial purposes described in the Use of Information section above. We share this information with the categories of third parties described in the Sharing of Information section above. 

Barrett-Jackson does not “sell” the personal information we collect (and will not sell it in the future without providing a right to opt out). We do use cookies and related technologies set by other companies to send targeted ads, as further described in the Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others section above. However, based in part on how we have set up their technologies, these companies have committed to only use the data they receive via our Services for the limited business purpose of providing advertising services to us. 

Subject to certain limitations, the CCPA provides California consumers the right to request to know more details about the categories or specific pieces of personal information we have collected in the last 12 months (including about information we disclosed for a business purpose), to delete their personal information, to opt out of any “sales” that may be occurring, and to not be discriminated against for exercising these rights. California consumers may make a rights request by emailing us at [legal@barrett-jackson.com](mailto:legal@barrett-jackson.com). 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: Barrett-Jackson Legal Department, 15555 North 79th Place, Suite A, Scottsdale, AZ 85260, or legal@barrett-jackson.com or 480.421.6694. 

__Back to Top
